ibiza-voice.com 2010-12-26

# Privacy policy

ibiza-voice.com takes your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy

. 

**What This Privacy Policy Covers**

  * This policy covers how ibiza-voice.com Treats personal information that ibiza-voice.com collects and receives, including information related to your past use of ibiza-voice.com products and services. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available. 

  * This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that ibiza-voice.com does not own or control, or to people that ibiza-voice.com

**Information Collection and Use**

**General**

  * ibiza-voice.com collects personal information when you register with ibiza-voice.com, when you visit ibiza-voice.com pages or the pages of certain ibiza-voice.com partners, and when you enter promotions or sweepstakes. ibiza-voice.com may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business partners or other companies. 

  * When you register we ask for information such as your name, email address. . Once you register with ibiza-voice.com and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us. 

  * ibiza-voice.com collects information about your transactions with us and with some of our business partners. 

  * ibiza-voice.com automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, ibiza-voice.com cookie information, and the page you request. 

  * ibiza-voice.com uses information for the following general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see, fulfils your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients. 

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**

  * ibiza-voice.com does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or other companies 

  * ibiza-voice.com displays targeted advertisements based on personal information. Advertisers (including ad serving companies) may assume that people who interact with, view, or click on targeted ads meet the targeting criteria . 

  * ibiza-voice.com does not provide any personal information to the advertiser when you interact with or view a targeted ad. 

**Cookies**

  * ibiza-voice.com may set and access ibiza-voice.com cookies on your computer. 

**Confidentiality and Security**

  * We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs. 

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

  * ibiza-voice.com may update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your ibiza-voice.com account or by placing a prominent notice on our site. 

**Questions and Suggestions**

If you have questions or suggestions, please complete a **feedback form**

Effective Date: January, 2001
